Questions = [
    {
        "Question": "What does \\n do in python?",
        "A1": "(A): Tabs over five spaces",
        "A2": "(B): Turns a number into a negative",
        "A3": "(C): Moves to a new line",
        "A4": "(D): Nothing",
        "Correct": "A3" 
    },
    {
        "Question": "What would the following data type be called: 5.5?",
        "A1": "(A): Integer",
        "A2": "(B): String",
        "A3": "(C): Boolean",
        "A4": "(D): Float",
        "Correct": "A4"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What would be the output of '7' + '3'?",
        "A1": "(A): '73'",
        "A2": "(B): 10",
        "A3": "(C): 73",
        "A4": "(D): error",
        "Correct": "A1" 
    },
    {
        "Question": "What do you use to install packages in Python?",
        "A1": "(A): NPM",
        "A2": "(B): NPX",
        "A3": "(C): PIP",
        "A4": "(D): YARN",
        "Correct": "A3" 
    },
    {
        "Question": "How do you define a function in Python?",
        "A1": "(A): def <name> (args):",
        "A2": "(B): function <name> (args) {}",
        "A3": "(C): function <name> (args):",
        "A4": "(D): def <name> (args) {}",
        "Correct": "A1" 
    },
    {
        "Question": "How do you import a variable from another file?",
        "A1": "(A): import <variable> from <file name>",
        "A2": "(B): from <file name> import <variable>",
        "A3": "(C): <variable> = <file name> ",
        "A4": "(D): from <full path to file> import <variable>",
        "Correct": "A2" 
    },
    {
        "Question": "What function can be used to display information for a user?",
        "A1": "(A): input()",
        "A2": "(B): len()",
        "A3": "(C): show()",
        "A4": "(D): print()",
        "Correct": "A4" 
    },
    {
        "Question": "What function can be used to prompt users for information?",
        "A1": "(A): prompt()",
        "A2": "(B): ask()",
        "A3": "(C): input()",
        "A4": "(D): print()",
        "Correct": "A3" 
    },
    {
        "Question": "What would the following data type be called: [4, 7, 6, 300, 8, 45 ]",
        "A1": "(A): list",
        "A2": "(B): array",
        "A3": "(C): dictionary",
        "A4": "(D): boolean",
        "Correct": "A1" 
    },
    {
        "Question": "What would be the output of pprint('This is the last question, you got',9, 'correct so far!!",
        "A1": "(A): 'This is the last question, you got 9 correct so far!!",
        "A2": "(B): 'This is the last question, you got,9correct so far!!'",
        "A3": "(C): 'This is the last question, you got9correct so far!!'",
        "A4": "(D): error",
        "Correct": "A4" 
    },
            ]


